older people I'm not making fun older
people yes I am actually I think this
whole joke makes fun of them it's ok
they've been a bit for eight hours all
right we're good
they went a bit right after Mayberry RFD
three people got that reference okay
great
no I do I love old folks man but I'm
always getting stuck behind that old guy
driving the Ford tortoise or whatever
they drive blinkers been on since he
bought the car you know the guy
you can always tell when it's a really
old guy cancer because they all have the
same silhouette where the ears get twice
as big as the head come on they grow
like summer squash 2885 man
my grandpa makes Ross Perot look like
Vincent van Gogh do weird stuff when you
get on my gram they're kind of streaks
every year anybody else got grandma's
like that they get smaller again my
grandma just turned 98 she's about that
big her and Grandpa go the movies he
says sneaks are in his hair works out
really good